(Raj:)Our dreams are very small,
aren't they?
(Sheldon:)Good news, gentlemen.
I have tentatively accepted...
ALL:
Yeah!
(Sheldon:)...the invitation
to join the Arctic expedition.
- It's not gonna be the same without you.
- We're gonna miss you.
(Sheldon:)Thank you,
but your sentiments may be premature.
(Raj:)Oh, I don't like where this is going.
(Sheldon:)I would like to propose...
(Sheldon:)...that the three of you
accompany me.
(Leonard:)- To the North Pole?
- Yes.
(Raj:)Is this just so we won't touch your stuff
while you're away?
(Sheldon:)I'll admit that was a concern.
(Sheldon:)But the fact is, I'll need a support team
and the three of you are my first choice.
- Really?
- Others might be more qualified...
(Sheldon:)...but the thought of interviewing them
gave me a stomachache.
(Sheldon:)I know I'm proposing
an enormous undertaking...
(Sheldon:)...so why don't you take a few moments
to discuss it?